voice.pk 2018-05-31

# Privacy Policy - Voice.pk

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for all pages and services offered by **Voice.PK (Voice of Pakistan)**

**» Personally Provided Information  
**

You do not have to give us personal information to visit **Voice.PK (Voice of Pakistan)**. If you choose to provide us with additional information through an e-mail message, inquiry form, comments, etc., we will only maintain the information as long as needed to respond to your question, inquiry, or to fulfill the stated purpose of the communication. Except for authorized law enforcement investigations, we do not give, share, sell or transfer any personal information to a third party.

**» Website Traffic Analysis Software  
**

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, we employ software programs to monitor traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. We also monitor our traffic to analyze visitors’s information, such as, but not limited to, operating system, browsers, screen resolutions and similar.

In the event of authorized law enforcement investigations, and pursuant to any required legal process, information from these sources may be used to help identify an individual.

**» Free E-mail Newsletters**

If users wish to subscribe to our e-mail newsletters, we ask for contact information. Our Daily Newsletter is powered by FeedBurner, however we use in-house solution for weekly Newsletter. We/Feedburner use information submitted by you in the same manner as we use contact information described above. Recipients of our newsletters can unsubscribe using the instructions listed at the end of the e-mail newsletter.

**»  **Third Party Advertising Partners

All users of  **Voice.PK (Voice of Pakistan)**  must keep this in mind that third parties may be placing and reading cookies on your browsers, or using web beacons to collect information as a result of ad serving on our website.

For, instance one of our partners, Google uses the [ DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) on **Voice.PK (Voice of Pakistan)** displaying Google AdSense for content ads. Similarly, other advertising partners may use their respective cookies to track advertising stats.

**» External Links**

Our web sites contain links to other sites.  **Voice.PK (Voice of Pakistan)** is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each web site to which we may link that may collect personal information.

**» Disclaimer:**

Mostly News, Articles and Images are not under our copyrights, these belong to their respective owners. News, Images and Articles have been taken from different sources, If anything is offensive or under your Copyrights then please E-mail us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) to get it removed.

Note: This Page can get updated any time, without an prior notice, so keep checking back.
